http://www.glenmary.org/privacy-policy/

Home / Privacy Policy
Glenmary Home Missioners does not share or disclose information about your individual visits to our Web site with any outside organizations nor do we automatically capture personal e-mail addresses. When information is provided to us through the web site, via the mail or on the telephone, we do not share that information with any third parties, except vendors hired to perform functions on our behalf. We will only use your personal information for the purpose for which it is submitted to us, such as to reply to an email and to process donations and requests for other materials offered by Glenmary Home Missioners. Glenmary does not sell or trade donor information with other non-profit organizations.
We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology to protect the transmission of information you submit to us on secure forms (such as credit card numbers or other personal identifiable information). While we use SSL encryption provided by Authorize.Net to protect your information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information offline. All the information you provide through our forms is stored securely.
Computer Tracking and Cookies
Our Web site is not designed to track, collect or distribute personal information not entered by visitors or donors. Our site logs do generate certain kinds of non-identifying site usage data, such as the number of hits and visits to our sites. This information is used for internal purposes by technical support staff to help enhance our Web site and offer better content to our visitors. While these statistics may be shared with others, the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information.
Help Us Keep Your Personal Information Accurate
If your personal information changes or you would like to review the personal information we may have on file for you, please contact us. Please provide your name and address, as well as how you initially submitted your personal information.
Physical Address
Mailing Address
4119 Glenmary Trace
Fairfield, OH  45014
P.O. Box 465618
Cincinnati, OH  45246-5618
Every day I realize how blessed and privileged I am to be a Glenmary Home Missioner. I get to enter sacred spaces with my encounters and interactions with the people of God.
- Brother Jason Muhlenkamp, Glenmarian
Taking a trip to the missions taught me that I can’t take my faith and the ability to practice that faith for granted.
- Rita M., Glenmary supporter.
The amazing thing about being a Glenmary volunteer is that the Glenmary spirit of ecumenism and charity is everywhere.
- Alyson M., mountain manager at Toppa Joppa, Grainger County, Tenn.
Many times, the faith and dedication of the people of the missions humbled me and challenged me to rededicate myself to our missionary work.
- Father Aaron Wessman, Glenmarian
Support the Mission Fund with the amount of:
$25
$50
$75
Other
